-你叫什么名字  -Ben  带我一起走吧
- What's your name?  - Ben. take me with you.
如果你真的想这么做  Ben
If that's what you really want, Ben--
如果你真的想  我希望你考虑一下
If that's what you want--i want you to think about that...
你要非常有耐心
You're gonna have to be very, very patient.
你是否想要保护你的朋友们  Sayid
You wanna protect your friends or not, Sayid?
我是Sayid Jarrah  大洋航空六人组之一
I'm Sayid Jarrah, one of the oceanic six.
站住
Stop right there!
Sayid
Sayid?
闭嘴  给我蹲下
Shut up! Get down.
再说一句  我要你命
Say another word, and you're dead.
我给你带了三明治  你也是敌人吗
I brought you a sandwich. are you a hostile?
-你觉得呢  -你叫什么名字
- Do you think I am?  - What's your name?
Sayid
Sayid.
我是Ben
I'm Ben.
见到你很高兴  Ben
It's nice to meet you, Ben.
提克里特  伊拉克
Tikrit, Iraq
过来
Come on.
你已经不是孩子了
You are not a child anymore.
要有个男人样
Act like a man.
你必须杀一只
You must kill one
我不想这么做
I... I don't want to.
按你父亲说的做
You will do as your father asks.
不要
No!
听我说
Listen to what I'm tell you !
快  杀掉一只
Come on , Kill one of them.
下手了再回去
You will stay outside until you do!
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： Isaac  zhjing  penny  三棵树   后期： 天空
时间轴： 死心塌地   校对： 非燕  许愿   总监： 非燕
■
做的好  你成功了
Good for you.you did it.
不是我做的
It wasn't me.
好吧  但至少有个人会成为男子汉
Well. At least one of you will be a man.
干的好  Sayid
Well done ,Sayid
Phil
Hey, Phil.
我又给他带了块三明治
I brought another sandwich for him.
这次是鸡肉沙拉的
Chicken salad this time.
我觉得不是食谱的问题
Yeah, I don't think it's the menu.
他不会吃的  别给自己添麻烦  孩子
He's not eating. Save yourself the trouble, kid.
是Horace叫我这么做的
But Horace told me to.
他为什么这么关心  这人是个敌人
Why does he care so much? The guy's a hostile.
-可这并不代表他不会饿  -随便了
- That doesn't mean he's not hungry. - Whatever.
我给你带了块三明治
I brought you a sandwich.
还有一本书
And a book.
我读了两遍
I read it twice.
挺不错的
It's good.
谢谢
Thank you.
是Richard叫你来的吗
Did Richard send you?
Richard
Richard.
他是你的头  对吧
He's your leader, right?
那只是个监视器
It's just a camera.
他们能看见  但听不见
They can see, but they can't hear.
四年前  我跑进了丛林
Four years ago, I ran away into the jungle,
后来Richard找到了我
And Richard found me.
我说我想离开这儿
I said I wanted to leave
并且加入你们
That I wanted to join you.
所以我耐心等待
So I've been patient.
如果你也有耐心的话
And if you're patient, too,
我应该可以帮你
I think I can help you.
莫斯科
Moscow.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
他想贿赂我
He tried to bribe me.
-可我不吃那套  -那必然
- It didn't work.  - Of course it didn't.
现在去哪
Where to now?
哪也不去
Nowhere.
-你干完了 -什么意思
- You're done.  - What do you mean, I'm done?
我们完工了
We're done.
Andropv是最后一个
Andropov was the last one.
你已经了结了
You've taken care of everyone
所有对你朋友造成威胁的人
Who posed a threat to your friends.
跟你合作很愉快  Sayid
It's been a pleasure working with you, Sayid.
就这样了吗
So that's it?
我帮你杀了那些人
I killed all those people for you
你就如此扬长而去
And now you're just... w-walking away?
你不是为我卖命  Sayid
You didn't kill them for me, sayid.
是你自己要他们的名字的
You're the one that asked for their names.
Widmore的组织人员已经全被歼灭
There's no one else in Widmore's organization
我们不必再追杀他们
That we need to go after.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
那我现在做什么
What do I do now?
我觉得你应该回到自己的生活
I suppose you should go live your life.
你自由了  Sayid
You're free, Sayid.
把你的手伸出来
Put out your hands.
快点
Come on.
谢谢
Thank you.
真高兴最终能听见你的声音
It's nice to finally hear your voice.
我是Horace
I'm Horace.
现在你该告诉我们你的名字了
Now's the part where you tell me your name.
你得告诉我你在丛林里做什么
I need you to tell me what you were doing out in that jungle.
-问他那模型的事 -Radzinsky 让我来说
- Ask him about the model. - I-- Radzinsky. I got this.
那些手铐
Those handcuffs--
你和你的人之间出了什么问题吗
Are you having some kind of problem with your people?
因为你们之间有了分歧
Because either you were in some kind of disagreement,
所以让我来帮你
Which makes me wanna help you,
又或者你是来做卧底的
Or you're a spy trying to infiltrate us.
到底是什么
So which is it?
好吧
Okay.
我给你一个小时考虑
I'm gonna give you an hour to decide
看你是否会告诉我
Whether you wanna talk to me.
如果你闭口不谈
But if you decide you don't want to...
不要怪我做绝了
Then I'm gonna have to take this to the next level.
你的培根好了
I think your bacon's ready.
我忘了
I forgot.
电视里演什么呢
What's on the tv?
结束了  不是吗
It's over, isn't it?
什么结束了
What's over?
这个
This.
我们  开始过日子了
Us... playing house.
所有的一切
All of it.
我从没想过他们会回来
I never actually thought they'd come back.
他们回来了  什么也没变
So they're back. nothing's changed.
Sayid要是告诉他们自己的身份了怎么办
What if sayid tells them who he is?
Sayid会守口如瓶
Sayid ain't sayin' nothin'.
不会出乱子的
I got this under control.
早上好  H
Morning H.
-Juliet -Horace
- Juliet.  - Horace.
我刚跟那囚犯谈了  现在有个问题
I just spoke to the prisoner. We have a problem.
怎么了  他说什么了
Why? what'd he say?
什么也没说  所以我才担心
Nothing, which is what worries me.
我们得知道他为何打破休战协议
We need to find out why he violated the truce,
他为什么来我们的领地
Why the hell he would come into our territory.
我得让Oldham来拷问他
I'm just gonna have to have Oldham do his thing on him.
那个精神病吗  不可以
That psychopath? no way!
我还有什么选择余地
What choice do I have?
就让他自己一个人待着
Just let me have go at him alone.
随便  不过我告诉你
Be my guest, but I'm telling you, man,
他不会说的
He is not gonna talk.
他会跟我说的
Oh, he'll talk to me.
-Lafleur先生 -去吃午餐吧  Phil
- Mr. Lafleur.  - Take your lunch, Phil.
你要自己进去吗
You going back there alone?
去吃午餐  Phil
Take your lunch, Phil.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
你怎么样了
How you doing?
一个12岁的Ben Linus
A 12-year-old Ben Linus
给了我带了个鸡肉沙拉三明治
Brought me a chicken salad sandwich.
-你觉得我该怎么办  -他很可爱吧
- How do you think I'm doing? - Sweet kid, huh?
你怎么能和他住一起
How can you live with him here?
我别无选择
'cause I ain't got a choice.
真的吗
Is that so?
你在70年代生活三年后会有什么感觉
Let's see how you feel after 3 years of living in the '70s.
算你运气好
Lucky for you...
我用这段时间爬到这个位置  来救你
I spent that time getting myself in a position to save your ass.
对不起  Sayid
I'm sorry, Sayid.
-干什么  -我告诉他们你会招供
- What are you doing? - When I tell them I got your confession,
我要他们相信你没有轻易屈服
I need them to believe that you didn't give it up easy.
-供认什么  -我们得串词  说你是来投奔我们的
- What confession?- We're gonna say you were trying to defect.
你要招出一些岛上居民的情报
You were gonna offer some intel on the others
才能融入我们
In exchange for living with us.
我怎么可能这样做
And why in god's name would I want to do that?
-否则我应该怎么办  -放我走
- What the hell else am I supposed to do with you? - Let me go.
然后呢  我不能就这样放了你
And then what? I can't just let you go.
为什么不
Why not?
因为这些人信任我
Because these people trust me.
我在这里营造了幸福生活
I've built a life here, and a pretty good one.
我放了你  这些就全完了
I let you go, all that goes away.
你要做出选择
So you got yourself a choice, chief.
要么合作并加入达摩组织
Either you cooperate and join the party in darmahville,
要么孤军奋战
Or you're on your own.
我选择孤军奋战
Then I guess I'm on my own.
新鲜饼出炉
Fresh show，the gratal.
他们尝试了不同的沙司口味
and they've tried different sauces.
他们真的很有一手
They are really up in hand
谢谢  Hurley
Thanks,Hurley
Sayid怎么样了
So, what's going on with Sayid
我毫不知情
I don't know anything yet.
什么意思
What do you mean you don't know any thing
我以为你和Saywer昨晚在一起
I thought you with saywer last night
他说了什么
What did he tell you
他叫我别打扰他  让他做自己的事
He told me leave him alone and let him do his job
你就这么做了吗
And you are going to?
我要和Juliet谈谈  看看她会不会告诉我
I'll talk to Juliet and see would she can tell me
Sawyer没有说  Juliet又怎么会说呢
Sawyer didn't tell you anything.Why would Juliet
她又怎么会说呢
why wouldn't she
因为他们在一起
Coz they're together
在一起是什么意思
What do you mean together
他们两情相悦  他们住一起  但不仅是室友
Together. They lived together and not like roommates
就像你们曾经这样
Together like you guys were
这很明显
That was obvious.
谁能预见这点呢
I mean who can see that coming
Hurley
我还是去烧几个煎饼吧
Well, I guess I better go make some more waffers.
你知道这件事吗
Did you know?
知道
Yeah.
你知道我想不通什么吗
You know what I can't figure out?
你怎么会被抓的
Is how the hell you got caught.
你们是"丛林之王"
You hostiles are supposed to be the kings of the jungle.
你怎么会笨到被这些白痴抓住呢
And how dumb are you that you got captured by these idiots?
而你是他们中垫底的
And yet you're the one who mops up after them.
好吧
Yeah, well...
我们等着瞧你被Oldman修理后的样子
We'll see how cute you are once oldham gets done with you,pal.
你在这做什么
What the hell are you doing here?
我给你送个三明治
I was bringing you a sandwich.
三明治
A sandwich?
你从没给我做过三明治
You never made me a sandwich in your life.
是啊  我是给自己做的
Yeah, well... I-I made one for myself...
-所以我想带给你  -是吗
So...So I just thought that I'd bring you - Oh, yeah? You just...
-爸爸  不要  -别对我撒谎
-Dad, don't!- Don't you lie to me.
你来这干什么
What are you doin' down here?
你是为他做的三明治  是不是
You made this sandwich for him, didn't you?
是的
Yes.
-谁让你这么做的  -没有人
- Who told you to do that?- nobody.
-没有人吗  -我只是想
- Nobody?- I just thought that--
你"只是想"  是吧
You "just thought," huh?
回家去
Go home.
快走  我会帮你洗脑
Go on. I'll tell you what to think.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
到处看看
I looked.
你想干什么  Ben
What do you want, Ben?
John Locke死了
John Locke is dead.
我想他是被谋杀的
I think he was murdered.
怎么会有人杀他
Why would anyone kill him?
我觉得是报复
I'd say it was retribution
我们俩做的事情
For the work you and I have been doing.
你很危险  Sayid
So you're in danger, Sayid.
如果我能找到你  那些人也能找到Locke
If I can find you, so can the people that found locke--
那些人  我们说话这会儿
The same people who, even as we speak,
正坐在Hugo的精神病院外面
Are sitting outside Hugo's mental institution.
他们在监视他吗
They're watching him?
整个星期都有人在那儿的
A man in a sedan has been there all week,
坐等
Just waiting...
你我现身
Presumably for you or me to show our faces.
所以你来这里
And that's why you're here?
你大老远来是想我杀了他吗
You actually came all this way to suggest that I kill this man?
你不想吗
You don't want to?
你为什么觉得我想
What makes you think I want to?
因为  Sayid
Because, Sayid...
简单的说
To put it simply--
你的绝活无人能及
You're capable of things that most other men aren't.
你做的每个选择
Every choice you've made in your life,
无论是谋杀还是拷问
Whether it was to murder or to torture,
都不是真正的选择
It hasn't really been a choice at all, has it?
这是你的天性  你的本质
It's in your nature. It's what you are.
你是杀手  Sayid
You're a killer, Sayid.
我不是你想的那样
I'm not what you think I am.
我不喜欢杀人
I don't like killing.
好吧  那我道歉
Well, then I apologize.
我看错你了
I was mistaken about you.
最后一次机会
All right, last chance.
你有什么要说的吗
You got anything to say?
把他带到Oldham那里
Take him to Oldham.
Oldham
Oldham.
准备好了吗
Hey, man. are we ready?
他是谁
Who is that man?
你的翻版
He's our you.
最好把他绑好  固定住
Better put him in the restraints.
别担心
Don't worry.
这是为了保护你的
They're for your protection.
我要给你的东西会有副作用
There are side effects to what I'm giving you.
撬开他的嘴
Open his mouth.
张开
Open up.
别怕
Don't be afraid.
转移注意力  让它起作用吧
Just turn your mind off. let it take effect.
你无法控制住
It's beyond your control,
反抗只会更消耗你的能量
So fighting it is a poor use of your energies.
无论你是否挣扎  有一件事是确定的  朋友
Whether you struggle or not, one thing's for sure, friend.
你会告诉我们真相
You will tell us the truth.
有人在洛杉矶
There's somebody-- Somebody here in los angeles.
-我带你们去见他  -谁
- Let me take you to them.- Who?
就是告诉我们
The same person that's gonna show us
-怎么回小岛的那个人  -是这样吗
- How to get back to the island.- is that what this is about?
太疯狂了  你们都疯了
This is insane. you are all crazy.
Sayid  你去哪
Sayid, where are you going?
我不参与这事
I don't want any part of this.
如果我再看见你
And if I see you again,
我们俩都不会愉快的
It'll be extremely unpleasant for us both.
你有菜单吗
Ahh. do you have a menu?
给你
There you go.
先生  还要MacCutcheon吗
Sir? another maccutcheon?
好的  谢谢
Please.
你有什么烦心事
What's that run you?
什么
Excuse me?
苏格兰酒
That Scotch.
那酒是怎么回事
What's a glass of that run you?
不管那是什么  都很值
Whatever it is, it's worth it.
我不理解
I don't understand
为什么会有人花120元买一杯饮料
Why someone uld pay 120 bucks for a glass of anything.
如果你知道我的酒的价格  为什么还要问我
If you knew what my drink cost, why did you ask me?
和我不在饭桌上  却在这里用餐原因相同
Same reason I'm eating my dinner here instead of a table.
给我一份半熟的牛眼肉
I'll have the rib eye, bloody.
好的  女士  一份半熟牛排
Yes, ma'am. rib eye, bloody.
你是职业的吗
Are you a professional?
职业的什么
A professional what?
你觉得我是个妓女吗
You think I'm a prostitute?
我不是妓女  我只是
I'm not a professional anything. I just...
觉得你看起来很忧郁
Thought you looked sad.
我喜欢忧郁的男人
I like sad men.
很遗憾听到你这么说
I'm sorry to hear that.
那么
So...
除了在酒吧独自饮酒
Other than drinking alone at bars...
你是做什么的
What do you do?
谋生行业
For a living.
我正在找工作
I'm between jobs at the moment.
那你之前做什么
So what did you do?
做我之前唯一擅长的事情
The only thing I was ever good at.
那你怎么不干了
Then why did you quit?
我在试着做些改变
I'm trying to change.
现在我知道你为什么忧郁了
I know why you're sad now.
是吗
Do you?
当你擅长于某件事的时候
When you are that good at something,
总会有一些人
There are always going to be people
诱惑你干老本行
Who tempt you into staying the same.
你怎么对诱惑了解这么多
And how do you know so much about temptation?
请我喝一杯威士忌  我就告诉你
buy me a glass of that scotch,and i will tell you
喂
Hello there.
Hello?
我要问你一些问题
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
我希望你放轻松  如实地回答我的问题
I want you to relax and answer them truthfully...
对此你别无选择
Not that you'll have any choice about it.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
Sayid
Sayid.
Sayid Jarrah
Sayid jarrah.
好的  Sayid
All right, sayid.
我们找到你的时候  你为什么带着手铐
Why were you in handcuffs when we found you?
因为
Because...
因为我是个坏人
Because I am a bad man.
你是要逃避你们的人的追捕
Were you running away from your people?
什么人
What people?
我们的敌人
The hostiles.
我不是你们的敌人
I am not a hostile.
那你是从哪里来的  Sayid
Then where did you come from, sayid?
乘飞机来的
I came on a plane.
什么飞机
What plane?
Ajira航空316号航班
Ajira flight 3-1-6.
我就是这么回到岛上的
And that's how I returned to the island.
"回到"  你之前来过这里吗
"returned"? you've been here before?
是的
Oh, yes.
第一次
The first time,
我乘坐的是大洋号815航班
I was on oceanic flight 8-1-5.
它坠毁了
It crashed.
我曾经在这里呆过100天
I was here for a hundred days.
然后我离开了
Then I left.
问问Saywer
Ask sawyer.
-谁是Sawyer  -管他呢
- Who's "sawyer"? - Who cares?!
这些都不重要  问问他关于火焰站的事
None of this matters. ask him about the flame.
安静点
Quiet.
你对我们这儿的站点知道多少
What do you know about our stations here?
我知道火焰站是个通讯站
I know the flame was a communication station.
珍珠站用来监视其他的站点
The pearl was to observe other stations.
天鹅站用来研究电磁学
The swan was to study electromagnetism.
但是  当然了  这是在事故发生之前
But, of course, that was before the incident
天鹅站? 他怎么知道我们准备取的名字
The swan? How could he know what we were gonna name it?
我们还没建成呢
We haven't even built it yet!
我告诉过你  他见过模型
I told you! He saw our model.
看见没有  他是个间谍  我早就知道
You see?! he is a spy! I knew it!
Radzinsky  我不想再说第二遍
radzinsky! I'm not gonna tell you again.
冷静
Cool it.
你们所有人都快死了
You're all going to die, you know.
什么
What?
你们会被杀光
You're going to be killed.
你怎么知道这些的  Sayid
How exactly would you know this, sayid?
因为我来自未来世界
Because I am from the future.
或许我该给你灌点药
Maybe I should've used half a dropper.
你
You...
你用的剂量刚刚好
You used exactly enough.
台式磨床  润滑油设备  钻床  都放在那边
Bench grinder, lube equipment, drill press over here.
插件  轴承  插座  棘轮  都放在这边
Plugs, bearings, sockets, ratchets here.
你这边四个引擎准备得怎么样
How are you with a flat four engine?
你不知道我在说什么  对吧
You have no idea what I'm talking about, do you?
不  不太清楚
no, not really.
没关系
It's okay.
Jack跟你说过我们的事
Jack told you about us...
没有  是Hurley告诉我的
No. hurley, actually.
这让我如释重负  真的
It's kind of a relief, actually.
我没想好该如何开口
I wasn't quite sure how to do it
又不让你感到我想打发你走
Without it sounding like I was telling you to stay away.
没事的
It's fine.
好吧
All right...
我们该怎么处置他
What do we do with him?
杀了他
We kill him.
等等  我们不杀人的  对吧
Hold on a second. we're not killing anyone, right?
他触犯了休战协定
He violated the truce.
你想如果他们抓住我们中的一个  怎么处置
What do you think they would do if they caught one of us?
从什么时候开始我们变得和他们一样了
Since when did we start acting like them?
-我们是文明人  -没错  我们是文明人
- We're civilized. - yes, we are.
我们有法律规则
We have a rule of law.
我们给了他很多机会替自己辩解
And we've given him every opportunity to defend himself.
需要我提醒你一下  这个人看见的太多
need I remind you, this man's seen things?
知道的太多  无需商榷
He knows things. there's nothing to talk about.
你确定他是个间谍吗  傻子
He's a spy. you sure about that, stu?
他当时正从敌人那里逃脱
He was trying to escape from the hostiles.
很显然他和他们的人之间有矛盾
He obviously has problems with his people.
没错  分享我们的秘密
Yeah, and sharing our secrets
是帮助他们解决问题最快捷的途径
Are the quickest way for him to solve those problems.
-我需要多点时间来考虑  -还要考虑
- Okay, I'm gonna need a little more time to consider. - consider?
我是说  他在这呆的时间越长
I mean, the longer he's among us,
我们就越危险
The--the more danger we're in.
我能和他谈谈  Horace  我只需要一点时间
I can talk to him, horace. I just need more time.
不  你有过一次机会了  Lafleur
No, you had your chance, lafleur!
为什么我们得听你的  Radzinsky
Why are we on your clock, radzinsky?
Horace  你得组织一次投票
Horace, you've got to call for a vote.
要不我们做个决定
Either we make a decision,
要不我打电话给Ann Arbor
Or I call ann arbor...
让他们替我们做决定
And they make it for us.
Radzinsky说得对
Radzinsky's right.
Horace  求求你
Horace, please...
我不能
I can't...
我不能提心吊胆地过日子
I can't sleep with one eye open.
我们现在有个孩子了
We have a baby now.
我们得为Ethan着想
We have to think about ethan.
我们得为这儿所有的孩子着想
We have to think about all the children here.
这个人在这里  我们怎么能有安全感呢
How are we going to feel safe with this man around?
我不知道他来做什么
I don't know what he's up to,
但是我们不能把他留在这儿
But we can't keep him here.
我么没得选
We have no choice.
好的
Okay.
让我们投票吧
Let's put it to a vote.
同意Radzinsky的
All in favor of Radzinsky's solution,
举手
Raise your hand.
Lafleur?
我真想说全票通过
I would really like to say it's unanimous.
我只想申明,我真的只在那里吃饭
Just for the record, I really was just there for dinner.
你怕我使坏吗
Are you afraid I'll get the wrong idea?
我觉得已经太迟了
I think it's too late for that.
脱掉吧
Take it off.
你再动  我就毙了你
You so much as flinch, and you're dead.
你是谁
So who are you?
你原先问我是不是个职业的
You asked me earlier if I was a professional.
我是个职业杀手  有人雇我把你带到关岛
I am a professional. I was hired to bring you to guam.
谁雇的你
Who hired you?
Peter Avellino家族
The family of Peter Avellino--
去年你残忍的杀害的那个男人
The man you killed in cold blood last year
在赛舍尔的高尔夫球场上
On a golf course in the Seychelles.
-你是赏金猎人  -我是谁不重要
- You're a bounty hunter? - Doesn't matter what I am.
你得得到报应
You're going to answer for what you've done.
给我一拳
Hit me in the face.
什么
What?
来吧  你欠我的  不管怎样  来吧
Go on. you owe me one anyway, so make it a good one.
然后我想让你拿走我口袋里的钥匙 然后逃走
Then I want you to take these keys out of my pocket And let yourself out.
外面的保卫是Phil  他是个笨蛋
The guard outside is Phil. he's a dimwit,
我知道 你能在他看见你出来前夺下他的枪
So I reckon you can get his gun before he even realizes you're out.
只要答应我不要伤他
Just promise me you won't shoot him.
我很感谢  但我在这不错
I appreciate the offer, but I'm fine right here.
他们想杀你
They're gonna kill you.
他们刚投了票  甚至那个年轻妈妈都想要你命
They just took a vote. even the new mom wants you dead.
我想呆在这  James
I'm going to stay here, James.
今天早上  你还求我放你
This morning, you were begging me to let you go.
为什么变了  因为...
Why would you change your-- because...
当我在丛林中醒来时
When I woke up in the jungle
我觉得我该回到这个岛上
And I realized I was back on this island...
没有原因
I felt there was no purpose to it.
但我现在真的知道为何我在这
But now I know exactly why I'm here.
为了挨枪子  还是别的原因
To get shot? then what?
你疯了
You're out of your mind.
你为何回来
Why'd you come back?
什么
What?
我满脑全是Sayid的话 他的原因都是废话
Sayid just filled my ear Full of some crap about his damn purpose,
我想知道你为何回来
And I wanna know... why'd y'all come back?
为何  Kate
Why, Kate?
我不知道为何其他人回来
I don't know why everyone else came back.
我只知道我为何回来
I just know why I did.
那是怎么了
What the hell?!
你还好吗
Are you ok?
Craig  拿上扳手  打开阀门  接上软管
Craig! grab a wrench, open those valves. get the hoses going.
好的
Okay.
Erin  拿上灭火器
Erin, grab the fire gear!
Bill  去帮Craig
Bill, go help Craig.
到底怎么回事
What the hell happened?
三年都没有公交车着过火  你们就来了一天
Three years--no burning buses. y'all are back for one day...
去拿那软管
Get on that hose.
给你软管
Man this hose!
推走它
Push it out!
各安全部门  我是Lafleur  我这失火了
All security! all security! this is Lafleur! we have a fire!
所有人到15号楼
Everyone get to building 15 now!
收到  这就过去
Roger that. I'm on my way.
你眼镜怎么了
What happened to your glasses?
我爸打的
My dad.
因为给我三明治
For bringing me the sandwich?
我明白
I know.
我爸也是个粗暴的人
My father was a hard man as well.
我真的恨这里
I really hate it here.
如果我放你出去
If I let you out...
能带上我吗
Will you take me with you,
到你们那
To your people?
好的  Ben  我会的
Yes, ben, I will.
这就是我来这里的原因
That's why I'm here.
你能保证我们能到关岛吗
Are you sure we're going to guam?
我们还能去哪里
Where else would we be going?
你能帮我个忙吗
Can I ask you a favor?
我们能坐下趟飞机吗
Can we get the next plane?
我坐飞机很迷信
I'm very superstitious when it comes to flying.
我给你到礼品店买个吉祥物
I'll buy you a rabbit's foot at the gift shop.
我们就坐这班飞机
This is the plane we're taking.
抱歉让你戴手铐  但至少我们都是干这行的
Sorry about the handcuffs, but at least we're in business.
等等  请等等  多谢你们给我留门
Hold up! wait, please! thank you for not closing it.
他在干吗  不  他不能过来
What's he doing here?! no, no, he can't come!
Hurley  如果你想回去
Hurley, hey, if you want to get back,
-这已成定局  -你是为Benjamin Linus工作吗
- This is how it's gonna have to be - Are you working for benjamin linus?
什么  你是为他工作吗
What? are you working for him?
谁是Benjamin Linus
Who's Benjamin Linus?
他是个骗子  幕后黑手
He's a liar, a manipulator...
为了保命 他对自己女儿都见死不救
A man who allowed his own daughter to be murdered To save himself...
这怪物专干屠杀
The monster responsible for nothing short of genocide.
为何我为这样的人工作
Why would I work for somebody like that?
我就做过
I did.
躲起来
Hide!
Jin
Jin?
Sayid
Sayid.
你在这干吗  你怎么逃出来的
What are you doing here? how did you get out?
Sawyer放我走的  他们想杀我
Sawyer let me go. they were going to kill me.
什么
What?
注意  犯人逃跑了
Attention. the prisoner escaped.
敌人逃跑了  提高警惕
The hostile is no longer in custody. be on the lookout.
他有武器  他们不知道他放了我
He could be armed. they don't know he released me.
拜托  Jin  我要继续赶路
Please, Jin, I need to keep moving.
好的
Okay.
让我先回话
Let me talk to him first.
Lafleur  我是Jin  快来
Lafleur, it's Jin here. come in.
你在哪学的那些
Where'd you learn to do that?
快来
Come on.
我们最好快走  他叫了Lafleur
We better go. he called Lafleur.
你没说错
You were right about me.
什么
What?
我是凶手
I am a killer.